A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, President, Colin G. Campbell papers, RG 2, Series 2 FA1300
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, President, Colin G. Campbell papers, RG 2, Series 2
1987-2000
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund
Campbell, Colin G.
FA1300
6.84 Cubic Feet 18 letter document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than twenty years old are open for research. Brittle or damaged materials are available at the discretion of RAC.
Biographical / Historical
Colin G. Campbell served as President of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund from 1988-2000.
Arrangement
Arranged in two subseries.
Subseries 1: Meeting Files.
Subseries 2: Trip Files.
Scope and Contents
Records primarily consists of Colin G. Campbell's files pertaining to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund Board of Trustees meetings and Committee meetings, including agendas, minutes and associated correspondence. Some meeting records have notes written by Campbell. This series also contains trip files from trips taken to Eastern and Central Europe as well as Asia.
- Meeting Files, 1
  - RBF Annual Meetings - Thailand, and Executive Committee Meeting, 1987 October 6, 1987 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 February 9 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1988 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1988 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting and Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1989 February 25 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting and Annual Meeting of Members, 1989 June 27 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 October 3 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1989 November 21 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1990 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 June 14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1990 October 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - RBF Audit Committee Meetings, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1991 February 12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1991 April 7 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1991 April 9 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1991 June 13 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1991 October 18 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1991 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - RBF Finance Committee and Board Meetings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
  - RBF Finance Committee and Board Meetings, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1993 March 9 (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1993 June 17 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1993 October 19 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1993 December 16 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1994 January 19 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1994 March 8 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1994 June 16 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Retreat, 1994 October 12 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1994 October 13 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting and Executive Committee Meeting, 1994 December 15 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1995 March 9 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1995 June 6 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - RBF Executive Committee Meeting, 1995 September 12 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1995 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting and Executive Committee Meeting, 1995 December 14 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1996 June (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1996 October (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1996 December 12 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1997 March 6 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1997 June 3 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1997 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1997 December 17 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1998 March 5 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2019
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1998 June 2 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1998 October 2 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1998 December 16 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999 March 4 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    Restricted - Open in 2020
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999 June 17 (Box 11, Folder 55-56)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999 October 15 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999 December 15 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 2000 March 9 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    Restricted - Open in 2021
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 2000 June 7 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - RBF Board of Trustees Meeting, 2000 October 17 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Trip Files, 2
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Polish American Freedom Foundation, 2000 March 10-14 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Colin G. Campbell's Personal Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Correspondence - Various Trips, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Foundation for the Development of Polish Agriculture, Warsaw, Poland, 1997 March 17-21 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Vienna, Prague, Kiev, Moscow, 1992 June 28-July 2 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - USA-Hungary Foundation Meeting, 1992 March 17-18 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Eastern Europe Trip Files, 1991 October (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - U.S. Foundations Meeting, 1991 January 11 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Bratislava Conference Report - Draft, 1990 August 23-25 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Victor Yaroshenko-Boris Yeltsin, 1990 June 30 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Meeting Re: Moscow and Budapest, 1989 October 25 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Boris Yeltsin Visit, 1989 September 9-23 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Dinner for Boris Yeltsin, 1989 September 11 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Budapest Meeting, 1989 July 31-August 2 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Eastern Europe Trip, 1988 October 27-November 12 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Hungary, Poland, Czechoslovakia, 1988 October 27-November 12 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Moscow, Tallinn, Helsinki, 1989 July 25-August 2 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Moscow - Foundations in the Soviet Union Seminar, 1989 July 26-28 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Colin Campell material Re: Philanthropy in the Soviet Union, 1989 July (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Moscow - International Seminar on Foundations, 1989 July 26-28 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Moscow - Seminar - Foundations in the Soviet Union, 1989 July 26-28 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - RBF Meeting on Foundations in the Soviet Union, 1988 September 7 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Soviet Foundations, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Eastern and Central Europe Trip Files - Visit to Estonia, USSR, 1989 July 29-August 1 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Malaysia Trip, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Vietnam Trip, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Asia Trip, 1995 October 24-November 3 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - International Conference on Supporting Nonprofit Sector in Asia: Asia Pacific Philanthropy Consortium, Bangkok, Thailand, 1998 January 9-11 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - David Rockefeller Jr. - Japan Trip, 1993 October (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Study Tour to South China and Indonesia, 1993 September 28-October 11 (Box 16, Folder 92-93)
  - Hong Kong - Taipei Trip Files, 1993 January 6-20 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Japan Visit, 1991 March 2-7 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Symposium on U.S.-Japan Exchange, 1991 February 21-22 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Symposium on Poverty Alleviation in the 1990s, Tokyo, Japan: Sasakawa Peace Foundation, 1990 March 5-6 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Indonesia Trip, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - China, Japan, Philippines Trip, 1990 February 22-March 12 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Dialogue on SINO-U.S. Relations (National Committee on US-China Relations), 1990 February 26-March 28 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Asia Trip with William McCalpin, 1989 February 25-March 12 (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - Ramon Magsaysay Awards Foundation - Trip Files, 1990-1996 (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - South Africa Trip, 1992 February 27-March 10 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - South Africa Trip, 1994 February 16-26 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - South Africa Trip, 1998 February 1-6 (Box 18, Folder 105)